A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1964-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files 1964-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1/1.981
This collection consists of 10,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply only to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library in 1998 August.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files from Dean Robert T. Canevari's office, including the files of the Associate Deans and Assistant Deans of Students.
Organization
Series I: Dean of Students, Robert T. Canevari Boxes 1-6
Series II: Associate Dean of Students, Sybil R. Todd/V. Shamim Sisson Boxes 7-20
Series III: Associate Dean of Students, Ronald Stump/Asst. Dean Michelle Samuels Boxes 21-26
Series IV: Restricted Files Boxes 27-28
Contents List
- Series I: Dean of Students, Robert T. Canevari
  - Mary Hall Betts Award 1996 (Box 1)
  - Gus Blagden Room 1995 (Box 1)
  - Council on Community 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Gray Carrington Screening Committee 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Gray Carrington Interviews 1995 (Box 1)
  - Distinguished Student Award 1995 (Box 1)
  - Exercise and Eating Habits 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Historic Renovations Corporation (2 folders) 1994-1996 (Box 1)
  - Lawn Steering Committee 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Search Committee--Director Newcomb Hall/University Union 1995 (Box 2)
  - Search Committee--Assistant Director for Operations for Newcomb Hall 1995 (Box 2)
  - Dean of Students Reception Reunion Weekend 1995 (Box 2)
  - Committee on University Union and Student Activities Building 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Rotunda Fire Research Committee--Lisa Guernsey 1995 (Box 2)
  - Program Budgets 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors (2 folders) 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Bad Check Committee 1990-1995 (Box 2)
  - Thursday Night Football Game 1995 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Master Planning Council 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Search Committee--Assistant Dean of Residence Life 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Student Activities Committee/Wide Awake 1995 (Box 3)
  - Office of Admissions 1993-1995 (Box 3)
  - Budget 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Capital Budget 1992-2002 (Box 3)
  - DATS 1992-1993 (Box 3)
  - Conflict of Interest Act 1987 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education, School of 1990-1992 (Box 3)
  - President's Retreat/Parents' Weekend 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Students Miscellaneous 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Personnel--Secretarial Job Descriptions 1986 (Box 3)
  - Interns--C. Sherman/M. Samuels 1995-1996 (Box 4)
  - DOS Request for Hiring Freeze Exemption 1995 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Concerns 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - DOS Retreat 1995 (Box 4)
  - Development-- Focus Group to Plan Capital Campaign Kick-off 1995 (Box 4)
  - Transfer Student Advisor Program 1991-1994 (Box 4)
  - ODOS Brochure 1991 (Box 4)
  - EO/AA Structure Report 1994 (Box 4)
  - Spring Meetings with Green and Ranningan re: Frats 1996 (Box 4)
  - University Functions Defined 1993 (Box 4)
  - Facilities, Use of 1987 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1995 1995 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1996 1996 (Box 4)
  - Graduation 1994-1996 (Box 4)
  - Graduate Roundtables 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - University Guide Service 1988-1993 (Box 4)
  - Handicapped/Disability Concerns 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - Housing 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council 1994-1996 (Box 4)
  - Inter-Sorority Council 1994-1996 (Box 5)
  - Intramural Fields 1990 (Box 5)
  - Jefferson Literary and Debating Society 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - University Committee on Judicial Policy 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Lower Lawn Reservation Requests 1995-1997 (Box 5)
  - Leadership 2000 1995 (Box 5)
  - Learning Needs and Evaluation 1987-1994 (Box 5)
  - Legal Adviser 1986-1994 (Box 5)
  - Longitudinal Study of Undergraduate Education 1989 (Box 5)
  - Newcomb Hall Renovations-- Miscellaneous 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Newspaper Articles 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - On Target Program 1990-1994 (Box 5)
  - Letter to Parents of First Year Students (and responses) 1988-1995 (Box 5)
  - Orientation 1995 (Box 5)
  - Directory for Parents and Academic Calendar 1986-1995 (Box 5)
  - Parents' Funding (2 folders) 1994-1995 (Box 5)
  - Resident Staff 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Request for Clerical Upgrade - RLO (Residence Life Office) 1986 (Box 6)
  - Residence Staff Appraisal Board (Restricted) 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Resident Staff Selections 1987-1993 (Box 6)
  - Residential Colleges--First Year Students 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Residential Colleges: Hereford College Report, Spring '94; Brown College Annual Report 1993-1994 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Security Policy 1989-1992 (Box 6)
  - Financial Aid, Office Of 1991-1993 (Box 6)
  - First Year Judiciary Committee 1984-1992 (Box 6)
  - Associate Dean of Students for the Residence Life Committee 1995 (Box 6)
  - Associate Dean of Students Search Committee (2 folders) 1995 (Box 6)
  - Escort Van 1986-1990 (Box 6)
  - Sexual Assault Resource Agency 1991-1993 (Box 6)
  - Student Concerns/Issues 1990-1992 (Box 6)
  - Summer Mailings 1994 (Box 6)
  - Student Protest 1986 (Box 6)
  - WTJU Radio Station 1993-1995 (Box 6)
  - Yellow Cab Letters (Restricted) 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Yellow Cab Referrals (Restricted) 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Paid Referrals (Restricted) 1994-1995 (Box 6)
- Series II: Associate Dean of Student, Sybil R. Todd/V. Shamim Sisson
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha 1990-1993 (Box 7)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 7)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee-- GCC Extension Subcommittee 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee 1996 (Box 7)
  - Academic Plan 1991-2000 (Box 7)
  - Southeastern Interfraternity Conference 1995 (Box 8)
  - SAMS (IFC/ISC Student Assistance Mentors) 1991-1996 (Box 8)
  - James Kern 1993-1995 (Box 8)
  - Board of Visitors 1987-1993 (Box 8)
  - Biennium Planning 1986-1994 (Box 8)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act 1990-1993 (Box 8)
  - Alcohol and Drug Awareness Week (2 folders) 1992-1994 (Box 8)
  - General Information 1988-1992 (Box 8)
  - Female Faculty Discussion on Race 1993 (Box 8)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Compliance Notices 1994 (Box 8)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee 1991-1993 (Box 9)
  - CIO Correspondence (2 folders) 1988-1991 (Box 9)
  - Will Keim Program 1994 (Box 9)
  - CIO (2 folders) 1987-1996 (Box 9)
  - ISC Executives R鳵m鳠(Restricted) 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Student Activity Fee 1994 (Box 9)
  - University Committee on Sexual Assault and Judicial Review 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - University of Washington Greek Row Report 1993 (Box 9)
  - On Target 1995-1996 (Box 10)
  - On Target Planning 1987-1991 (Box 10)
  - On Target Advisory Committee 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - On Target Advisory Board 1983 (Box 10)
  - On Target Fall Leadership Conference 1992 (Box 10)
  - On Target 1991-1994 (Box 10)
  - On Target Consulting 1991-1994 (Box 10)
  - On Target Retreat Materials 1990 (Box 10)
  - Programs--General Information 1988 (Box 10)
  - Consulting--General Information 1990 (Box 10)
  - Spring Retreat Stuff 1994 (Box 10)
  - On Target Ideas 1989-1991 (Box 10)
  - Risk Management Presentation at Greek Officers Orientation 1988 (Box 10)
  - OT Transition Retreat 1990 (Box 10)
  - On Target Members Information 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Information for new co-chairs 1990 (Box 10)
  - The Assemblage 1989 (Box 10)
  - On Target Newsletter 1988 (Box 11)
  - Mid-Year Retreat 1996 (Box 11)
  - On Target Fall Retreat 1995 (Box 11)
  - On Target 1994-1995 (Box 11)
  - Returning On Target Applications 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - On Target's Fall Leadership Conference 1995 (Box 11)
  - Ropes Course 1989 (Box 11)
  - OT Brunch 1990 (Box 11)
  - Student Organization Development Program - Surveys 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - SODC Committee 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Student Organization Development Program Budget 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Student Organization Development Committee 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Student Organization Development Survey 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - SODC Roster Mailing Labels 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - SODC Correspondence 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Student Organization Development Timeline and Memos 1988 (Box 11)
  - On Target Evaluation 1988 (Box 11)
  - Selections Information 1988 (Box 11)
  - On Target Open House Initiation 1988 (Box 11)
  - On Target Budget 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - On Target 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - On Target Spring Leadership Conference 1992 (Box 12)
  - On Target Selections 1991 (Box 12)
  - On Target Retreat 1991 (Box 12)
  - Assemblage 1990 (Box 12)
  - On Target Selections 1990 (Box 12)
  - On Target Selection Process 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - On Target Programming Committee--Seminar Evaluation 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - On Target Advisory Board 1990 (Box 12)
  - On Target Summary 1989 (Box 12)
  - Ropes 1990 (Box 12)
  - Emerging Student Leader Retreat 1989 (Box 12)
  - On Target Retreat 1992 (Box 12)
  - On Target 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Focus Leadership Conference 1991 (Box 12)
  - On Target Seminar 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Assemblage Evaluations n.d. (Box 12)
  - Social Host Liability Case n.d. (Box 12)
  - TIPS--Alcohol Education Program 1988 (Box 12)
  - Alcohol Policy 1989 (Box 12)
  - Alternatives Conference 1989 (Box 12)
  - Leadership Conference 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Fall Leadership Conference 1993 (Box 13)
  - On Target Retreat 1994 (Box 13)
  - "The Awakening" 1989 (Box 13)
  - Math Document (On Target) 1994 (Box 13)
  - On Target Consulting 1992-1993 (Box 13)
  - On Target (4 folders) 1992-1994 (Box 13)
  - First Report on the Status of Women--Prepared by Medical School Committee on Women 1990 (Box 13)
  - VIEW (Va. Intervention Education Weekend) 1990 (Box 14)
  - Varsity Park Fire 1990 (Box 14)
  - Teleconference: The Power of Caring 1990 (Box 14)
  - Proposal--Summer Leadership Conference 1990 (Box 14)
  - Student Summer Life Mailing 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Summer Leadership Program Responses 1992 (Box 14)
  - Recycling 1989 (Box 14)
  - Leadership Readings (2 folders) 1991-1994 (Box 14)
  - Licensing Study Committee 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Leadership Conferences 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - International Studies Program 1987-1990 (Box 14)
  - SODC Internship Program 1987 (Box 14)
  - ISC Informal Rush Workshop 1989 (Box 15)
  - ISC Pledge Workshop 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - National Interfraternity Conference 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Greek Week Foundation (AEII) 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Greek--CIO 1987 (Box 15)
  - Graduate Students 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - Drug Education 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Fire Safety 1988 (Box 15)
  - Alcohol Awareness Week (2 folders) 1989-1991 (Box 15)
  - Alcohol Awareness (2 folders) 1986-1991 (Box 15)
  - Graduate Study: Counseling, Psychology, Student Personnel 1989 (Box 16)
  - Graduate School Dean Meetings 1992 (Box 16)
  - FYS Participant Evaluations 1994-1995 (Box 16)
  - Graduate and Professional Students 1988-1992 (Box 16)
  - FYS Participant Evaluations 1997 (Box 16)
  - FYS Facilitator Exit Interviews 1997 (Box 16)
  - FYS Participant Evaluations 1996 (Box 16)
  - FYS Facilitator Exit Interviews (2 folders) 1994-1996 (Box 16)
  - Parents' Weekend 1995 (Box 16)
  - First-Year Seminar Session 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Parents' Weekend 1992 (Box 17)
  - Expansion 1989 (Box 17)
  - Exit Interviews 1995 (Box 17)
  - Exit Interviews 1996 (Box 17)
  - Community Space Availability 1993-1994 (Box 17)
  - Blue Ridge Mountain Rescue Group 1991-1995 (Box 17)
  - Assistant Dean of Students--Residence Life (1-3 of 5) 1994 (Box 17)
  - Assistant Dean of Students - Residence Life (4-5 of 5) 1994 (Box 18)
  - Assistant Dean of Students - Residence Life: Gerda, Janice 1994 (Box 18)
  - Assistant Dean of Students - Residence Life: Wilder, Jennifer A. 1994 (Box 18)
  - Assistant Dean of Students - Residence Life: McCurdy, Colleen 1994 (Box 18)
  - Assistant Dean of Students - Residence Life: Hill, Regina L. 1994 (Box 18)
  - Leadership 2000 Evaluations 1996 (Box 18)
  - Leadership 2000 Responses 1995-1996 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Football--Cavalier Volunteers 1988 (Box 18)
  - Student Group Database--GWIS 1993-1995 (Box 19)
  - Student Affairs Workload 1995 (Box 19)
  - Parking and Transportation Issues/Correspondence 1993 (Box 19)
  - Parking and Transportation Requests for Waivers and Responses 1996-1997 (Box 19)
  - Parking and Transportation 1990 (Box 19)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1980-1989 (Box 19)
  - Staff Meetings 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - Parents' Day Committee 1977 (Box 19)
  - Parents' Day 1978 (Box 19)
  - Parents' Day Activities and Plans 1979 (Box 19)
  - Parents' Day (3 folders) 1980-1982 (Box 20)
  - Parents' Weekend 1983-1991 (Box 20)
  - Mandatory Seminar for First Year Students 1992 (Box 20)
  - Leadership 2000 Notes 1990 (Box 20)
  - Leadership 2000 (2 folders) 1991-1993 (Box 20)
  - Leadership 2000 Operations 1993-1994 (Box 20)
- Series III: Associate Dean of Students, Ronald Stump/Assistant Dean of Students Michelle Samuels
  - ABC License Request by Darden 1993 (Box 21)
  - Alcohol Abuse and Male Gender Issues in the Fraternity System Grant 1993 (Box 21)
  - Alcohol Beverage Control Guidelines 1993 (Box 21)
  - Fall Semester Non-Alcohol Events 1993 (Box 21)
  - Graduation Garden Events 1996 (Box 21)
  - Nonacademic Rules and Regulations -- Alcohol Associated Citations n.d. (Box 21)
  - Working Document on the Alcohol Policy, Dining Services, NH and ODOS 1991 (Box 21)
  - ACPA Activities Listserver 1995 (Box 21)
  - Applications for Grants under the Comprehensive Program 1994 (Box 21)
  - Assessment of Off Grounds Students 1988-1995 (Box 21)
  - Asian American and African American Relations n.d. (Box 21)
  - Asian American Focus Groups 1994 (Box 21)
  - Asian American First Year Students Survey 1996 (Box 21)
  - Asian American Student Leadership Seminar 1994-1995 (Box 21)
  - Asian American Student Leadership Seminar 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Asian American Student Conference 1990-1995 (Box 21)
  - Asian American Student E-mail List 1994 (Box 21)
  - Asian American Student Leadership Seminar 1996-1997 (Box 21)
  - Asian/Asian American Leadership Conference Evaluations n.d. (Box 21)
  - Asian Leadership Council 1995 (Box 21)
  - Asian Perspectives 1996 (Box 21)
  - Asian Perspectives Weekend 1994 (Box 21)
  - Asian Perspectives Day 1995 (Box 21)
  - Asian Studies Enhancement 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - Asian Student Union 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Asian Student Union: a multi-faceted proposal for the advancement of diversity n.d. (Box 21)
  - Asian Student Union President 1994 (Box 21)
  - Atlantic Coast Asian American Students Union Conference 1994 (Box 21)
  - Canevari 1996 (Box 21)
  - First Year Asian American Leadership Seminar 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Former ASU Officers n.d. (Box 21)
  - The Balancing Act II 1995 (Box 21)
  - UVa Board of Visitors -- Student Affairs & Athletic Committee Meeting 1995 (Box 21)
  - The Bell Curve 1994 (Box 21)
  - Budget for Minority Student Programs 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - Campus Violence Prevention Center 1993 (Box 22)
  - Center for Survey Research -- UVa CSR 1995 (Box 22)
  - Choral Music Reservations 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Clinch Valley College Presentation on CIOs 1994 (Box 22)
  - A Comparison Between Administrators: Mindy Dalgarn & Ron Stump 1994 (Box 22)
  - General Planning Support Funds 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - General Planning Support Expenditures 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Comprehensive Fees Background 1964-1994 (Box 22)
  - Coordinator of Community Development Services 1994 (Box 22)
  - Cult Awareness Week n.d. (Box 22)
  - Cultural Programming Board 1995 (Box 22)
  - Darden Student Organizations Relationship Statement 1995 (Box 22)
  - Day on the Lawn/Spring Fling Planning Committee 1995 (Box 22)
  - DOS Orientation Programs -- Inventory 1994 (Box 22)
  - One Day Retreat 1995 (Box 22)
  - Office of the Dean of Students -- Committee Representation 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - Office of the Dean of Students -- Compliance with ADA n.d. (Box 22)
  - Dean of Students Organization Goals 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - Ronald J. Stump Responsibilities 1996 (Box 22)
  - Disabilities: Assessment of Student Life 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Disability Act Compliance n.d. (Box 22)
  - Student Organization Compliance with ADA 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Discrimination Policy 1985-1995 (Box 22)
  - Dining Services Presentation & Discussion on Illegal Entries into Contract Dining 1995 (Box 22)
  - University/Equity Initiatives 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Diversity Self Study 1995 (Box 22)
  - Affirmative Action Plan n.d. (Box 22)
  - Domestic Partners 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Committee 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Committee 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - Escort Services Advisory Committee 1985-1994 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Grievance Policy & Procedure 1995 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund 1993 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund 1994 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund 1995 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund 1996-1997 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Reports 1979-1992 (Box 23)
  - Family Educational Rights & Privacy Act 1993-1995 (Box 23)
  - Foster Home Archeology Dig 1994 (Box 23)
  - Free Speech on the Electronic Frontier 1995 (Box 23)
  - Graduate Advisors Presentation 1995 (Box 23)
  - Graduation Garden Events 1994 (Box 23)
  - Graduation Garden Events 1995 (Box 23)
  - Graduation Party 1994 (Box 23)
  - Graduation Party 1995 (Box 23)
  - Final Exercises 1996 (Box 23)
  - Finals Weekend 1994 (Box 23)
  - Finals Weekend 1995 (Box 23)
  - Letter to Graduating Class 1990-1994 (Box 23)
  - Guidelines for Student Organization Fund Raising Projects Conducted Outside Academic Faculty 1993 (Box 23)
  - Graduate/Professional Student Reception 1996 (Box 23)
  - Grassroots 1994 (Box 23)
  - Gray-Carrington Committee 1995 (Box 23)
  - Hereford College 1992-1996 (Box 23)
  - Honor Committee 1963-1996 (Box 23)
  - Presentation to Honor Educators 1995 (Box 23)
  - Integrity and Ethics: Why Should We Be Concerned? n.d. (Box 23)
  - International Center Advisory Council 1993 (Box 23)
  - International Center Advisory Group 1993 (Box 23)
  - International Studies 1993 (Box 23)
  - Jefferson Society Hearing, Spring 1993 (Box 23)
  - Lawn Approvals 1994-1995 (Box 23)
  - Leadership Group 1994-1995 (Box 23)
  - Protocol for Potential Judiciary Cases from Deans on Call 1996 (Box 23)
  - Late Night Event Policy 1992-1993 (Box 23)
  - Low Power TV Advisory Board 1994 (Box 23)
  - Luther P. Jackson Cultural Center 1993-1995 (Box 23)
  - Mediation in Sexual Assault Cases n.d. (Box 23)
  - Mediation Services n.d. (Box 24)
  - Memorial Gymnasium 1990 (Box 24)
  - Charlottesville Fathering Initiative 1996 (Box 24)
  - Men's Workshop -- New College 1994 (Box 24)
  - Monroe -- Newcomb Plaza n.d. (Box 24)
  - Mosaic House 1995 (Box 24)
  - Nelson S. Chow Award 1995-1997 (Box 24)
  - New Student Mailing 1994 (Box 24)
  - ADA Compliance in Orientation Activities 1994 (Box 24)
  - First Year Orientation Description 1988 (Box 24)
  - Graduate Student Brochure 1997 (Box 24)
  - Greeters 1994 (Box 24)
  - Mailings to Academic Deans on Orientation Schedules 1995 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Fee Proposal 1992 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Cost 1994 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Planning 1994 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Schedules 1994 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Announcements 1995 (Box 24)
  - Organization Fair 1995 (Box 24)
  - Student Council Activities Fair 1997-1998 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Correspondence 1995 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Evaluation 1995 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Planning 1995 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Schedules 1995 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Planning 1996 (Box 25)
  - Orientation Announcements 1996 (Box 25)
  - Orientation Brochures 1996 (Box 25)
  - June 9 Presentation on Multicultural Activities to Board of Visitors 1995 (Box 25)
  - Orientation Evaluation 1996 (Box 25)
  - Processions Subcommittee of the Commencement and Convocations 1995-1996 (Box 25)
  - Proctor and Gamble 1996 (Box 25)
  - Proposed On Grounds Fall Headcount Enrollment Plans 1996 (Box 25)
  - President's Reception for New Undergraduate Students 1994 (Box 25)
  - President's Retreat 1993 (Box 25)
  - President's Retreat 1994 (Box 25)
  - President's Retreat 1995 (Box 25)
  - President's Retreat 1996 (Box 25)
  - President's Retreat for Graduate Students 1994 (Box 25)
  - Psychological Hearings on Honor Offenses -- Chairperson's Opening Remarks (Restricted) 1994-1995 (Box 25)
  - Certain Cases Involving Psychiatric Issues n.d. (Box 25)
  - Publicity Service n.d. (Box 25)
  - Racial/Ethnic Groups Advertisement 1994 (Box 25)
  - Recognition of Student Organizations on Transcripts, Diplomas and Graduation Programs 1994 (Box 25)
  - Redefining Self Governance/Self Government n.d. (Box 25)
  - Regulations and Guidelines for Outdoor Areas 1995 (Box 25)
  - Reservations for the Academic School Year (forms) 1996-1997 (Box 25)
  - Renovation Rooms/Spaces 1996-1997 (Box 26)
  - Resident Staff Olympics 1993 (Box 26)
  - Monroe Residential College n.d. (Box 26)
  - Residential Life, Committee for 1993-1994 (Box 26)
  - Reunion Weekend 1994 (Box 26)
  - Rockfish Gap Report 1818 (Box 26)
  - Ropes course for new undergraduate students 1994 (Box 26)
  - Rotunda Reservation Form 1993-1996 (Box 26)
  - Public Information Activities Guidelines 1994 (Box 26)
  - Spanish Speaking Dining Table 1995 (Box 26)
  - Sexual Assault Resource Agency 1991-1994 (Box 26)
  - Self Study 1994 (Box 26)
  - Statement of Concern of Black Student Issues 1994 (Box 26)
  - UVa Street/Road Closings Approval Worksheet 1994-1997 (Box 26)
  - Street/Road Closings at UVa associated with special events 1994-1998 (Box 26)
  - Student Affairs Alumni Directory 1995-1996 (Box 26)
  - Student council Faculty Fellowship Program 1995 (Box 26)
  - William and Mary: Permission for pre-game party 1994 (Box 26)
  - Student Council Representatives -- Fall 1995 1995 (Box 26)
  - Student Life Talkshow 1994 (Box 26)
  - Student Organization Server 1995 (Box 26)
  - The Student Right to Know and Campus Security Act 1994 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence -- Stump 1995 (Box 26)
  - Ronald J. Stump Responsibilities 1994 (Box 26)
  - Summer Mailings 1995 (Box 26)
  - Summer Mailings 1996 (Box 26)
  - Survey of Multicultural Centers in Selected Universities 1994 (Box 26)
  - Survey -- Off Grounds Student Experiences 1996 (Box 26)
  - Targeting Excellence: UVa Self Study 1994-1996 (Box 26)
  - Telecommuting: Work at Home 1995 (Box 26)
  - Women's Leadership 1996-1997 (Box 26)
- Series III: Restricted Files Boxes 27-28 (Box Boxes 27-28)